(Here we go now) It's time to fly!
We've waited so long, let's touch the sky!
Are you ready for the best weekend ever?
Yeah, let's keep this energy together!
It’s been a long time since we’ve gotten together,
I hadn’t seen you since last summer, you know?
So I called you up and asked, "What are your plans for Friday?"
Can you make it out tonight?
You shouted, "I’d be down! Count me in, I'm in!"
I’ll see you at 12 o’clock on Friday
We’re having dinner around the corner tonight
The train leaves at 9, we're ready to go!
Pack your bags fast, let the high tension flow!
Let’s get ice cream and then go eat at the park!
We passed a cute cafe, so I decided to check it out!
We’re gonna make unforgettable memories
Yeah, we’re gonna laugh and dance until the dark!
Let’s get ice cream and then go eat at the park!
We passed a cute cafe, so I decided to check it out!
We’re gonna make unforgettable memories
Yeah, we’re gonna laugh and dance until the dark!
I’d like to make a reservation for two!
"What time? How many people?" the worker asked through!
I’d like an avocado and egg on rye, please
Oh, that sounds good, this food is amazing!
If you want to, you can try a bit of mine!
Let’s get ice cream and then go eat at the park!
We passed a cute cafe, so I decided to check it out!
We’re gonna make unforgettable memories
Yeah, we’re gonna laugh and dance until the dark!
Let’s get ice cream and then go eat at the park!
We passed a cute cafe, so I decided to check it out!
We’re gonna make unforgettable memories
Yeah, we’re gonna laugh and dance until the dark!
We have searched for this feeling for so long
And now we are right where we both belong
Every moment we share is like a bright spark
Illuminating our world and leaving a mark!
It’s going to be the best vacation ever!
See you on Friday, let’s keep this feeling forever!
Yeah, we’re gonna run, we’re gonna shine!
We’re gonna run, we’re gonna shine!
Yeah, we’re gonna shine until the dark!